Inari Experience Time! It's the Iginari experience time!
Please join us for the MUJI group's Star Dance, Iginari and House Dance!
I am Kitchin Shinchu!
My name is Miyu Furtado.
Pleased to meet you!
I'm Gotoon.
Who is it?
I don't know.
Well, these two are here today.
It's your first time, isn't it?
It's our first time.
It's our first time... together.
I didn't know that.
But last year you were the most active in the first season.
Yasumori was the first.
Is that right?
Second and third.
What? You came out the most?
I came in third.
You came in second.
I came in second. That's right.
That's right. So this year, it's Captain Yasumori.
Oh, really?
He's the best at it.
I'm the one who thought of this.
What will you two be doing today?
Today's exploration is...
The best date plan at E-Beans!
Well, E-Beans has a variety of stores.
I know I said "date plan," but...
What's the best way to enjoy E-Beans?
I asked the two of you to come up with a plan.
We're going to have them present their ideas today.
The two of you have been coming to E-Beans for quite a long time now.
Yes, they come here on their own time, too.
We go here in the morning, and here first thing in the morning.
Lunch is here.
What's with you, boss?
That one.
It's a new pose for the explorers.
I was going to be a general.
What are you writing?
I mean, you know, exploration.
Binoculars, like a telescope.
Maybe it'll just be for today.
No, we'll definitely do it. We do it every time.
Okay, so I've got two people who have come up with plans.
I'll ask them to introduce one by one.
Let's go.
GO!
Okay, first of all, Pearl, please give us your presentation.
We're at the Garden Terrace on the 4th floor right now.
The illumination is on right now.
The illumination is very couple-like.
I would like to start with Animate.
First of all, when you come here, you go to animate, just the two of you?
Yes, we'll go to Animate together.
After that, we go to the bookstore downstairs.
We'll browse through Jump at the bookstore.
It's a date, right?
Yes, it is.
What kind of date?
I have an after-school date with a student.
The theme.
Right, the theme.
That's why I have a student after-school date.
Browsing?
Yeah, we browse.
And say, "I like this scene.
I like it.
Even if we don't talk.
Wow!
What's the matter?
Are you stressed out?
Yeah, I'm stressed.
Oh, my God.
You know, it's like...
It's like the space doesn't bother you anymore.
Yeah, I like the idea of the two of us browsing together.
That's nice.
That air.
Browsing.
After you browse.
Come to this floor.
Come to the fourth floor, and we'll take a Purikura.
Just the two of us.
It's very student-like, isn't it?
Yes, we do.
I guess so.
Let's try Purikura.
Let's go.
This is the one for Tomball.
This time, we'll use this model.
Warm.
We're going to have a lot of fun.
Okay, so it's a date.
I'm not a good-looking guy.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no, no.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Why do you keep sticking your cheekbones out?
You look so handsome.
There it is!
There you go.
Why is it showing?
LOL!
Next...
More and more...
There it is!
Ta-da!
Two.
Two boxes.
One box.
Thank you.
And this one too.
LOL!
Here we go. Here we go.
Don't blindfold me.
I thought you were going to say it.
I'm sure you are.
I'm pretty sure I know what it is.
Have you ever done it before?
No, I haven't.
We're done.
Doodle time.
Next.
I wonder if that's the one.
LOL!
LOL.
Why is it like this?
I'll give you a Bedieland ticket for this one.
LOL!
Looks like you're having fun polo polo
LOL.
That's nice.
This is badass.
Super fun.
That's fun that's nice.
It's good.
Hey, it's not bad.
Laughing.
This one.
They're giving me this too.
That's right.
The latest one.
No! Outside.
Dirt like dirt.
My bangs are split.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's a backstage trick.
I'm not smiling.
Go ahead, laugh.
Oh, that's funny.
Is that what you're buying?
Three.
You write these things, right?
You write these things.
No, well, you're a pro.
Professional, man.
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I got a surprise for you.
There you go, there you go, there you go.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's a big boyfriend, isn't it?
No, he's definitely on the baseball team.
He's definitely on the baseball team.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
That's what I want.
This is so hard.
You're not very good at this.
Does that mean you like it?
But it's so hard.
What's this?
It's like a total kanji drama.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, it's funny.
It's done!
Oh!
Mutual.
Cell phone case.
Memories.
I see.
Thank you very much.
I'll put it on your forehead.
We should break up.
Ha-ha-ha.
Next, flape.
Flape.
Delicious.
Ta-da!
So, after taking purikura
I was a little hungry.
I'm going to eat this flape.I'll have a flape here.
At Mandoror
While eating crepes
I'm looking at the purikura I took earlier.
Yes, yes...
But we order only one crepe.
And then we share it.
The crust and the filling.
Why?
What do you do with the one that hits the crust?
They get a spoon and share it like this.
Dare I?
By the way, which one would you like to eat?
If it's one of these...
I think I'd prefer the deliberate one.
Around here.
We have this too.
We also have shrimp paste.
Wow!
And it's only available at the Sendai store!
Well, then...
Here...
Have a flape.
There's an "in-toy" too!
That's right.
I'm sure you'll find Ms. Singh's and Mr. Cullen's autographs on the wall.
While you're looking at this.
What a surprise!
Let them eat.
And have them look at the staff and the concentration.
He said the staff is coming out.
They can throw out the trash and stuff.
There's a washbasin right here.
You can wash your hands.
You can wash your face.
There's a marine plant.
This is not a crepe.
They poked me in the top.
That's a relief.
It's going to be fun.
Let them have fun.
After that...
I'd like to move on.
Yes, let's go.
Yes, so...
After eating crepes
I'd like to play a little at the rumble corner.
I'd like to play a little.
This course
Let's take a look.
What do you like?
Straps for the two of us.
Like matching straps.
You like that kind of thing?
Crepes.
Like eating the same thing.
She wants to be with her students.
They like to do things together.
Like they're all the same.
I'm not making fun of you.
No, I'm not.
I'm not messing with them.
Like this.
Or this.
I don't give a shit about your grandfather's shit.
Mame knowledge shit.
I really like
I like this kind of shit.
Cute kids, hot guys...
You have one of these?
It's a strap.
Doki-Doki Shark Panic?
You can play with it.
It's exciting, just the two of us.
What's more...
We can do this while we're waiting for Pilikula.
Do this.
The suribashi effect.
You get nervous.
You'll think you're in love.
I'll give it a try.
What color do you like?
Let's see what color you're going for.
Pyramid.
Okay, purple.
I'm gonna go with black.
Who's gonna get it?
I hope you get it.
That's what we're talking about.
You think this is it?
I think it's purple.
Open it.
Why the surprise?
Ta-da!
I got a gray one.
Exciting, isn't it?
Let's take turns.
Okay, I'll do it myself.
Thank you.Thank you.
Oh, oh, that hurts.
Jeez, that hurts.
Ew! Ew! Ew!
Oh, that hurts... that hurts.
Tonegay.
This couple that no one comes near
Oh, no!
Oh, no, I can't go in this mess corner.
I can't go in there.
Let's just play here.
If you do, let's just go with the flow, shall we?
What? Where are you going?
First basement.
This way, sir.
Ta-da!
This is the exit to the subway.
This is where we say bye-bye.
What?
On the subway.
Are you going home with me or dropping me off?
No, no.
It's not a good idea to go too far together.
I see.
It's definitely not a good idea.
I'll see you tomorrow.
But if you're a student, it's probably a good idea.
You have to go home and do homework and stuff.
It's the most fun on the way home.
That's right.
And then, when you're on the train...
Thank you for today.
There it is.
It's good to keep it simple.
I see.
That's good.
Students, please use this as a reference.
I see.
I did it.
That's all.
It's nice.
Next, let's go to Miyu's plan!
Yes!
This is Miu's plan.
Where is this?
This is the back side of E-Beans.
It's the back side of E-Beans, right?
The back entrance.
The entrance.
The optional entrance.
Yes, sir.
We'll meet here at 10:00 a.m.
That's the rotation. 10:00 a.m.?
Yes, 10:00 a.m.
E-Beans rotation time.
We'll meet at 10:00 a.m.
We have to be in at 10:00.
So we'll meet 10 minutes after 9:00.
Ten minutes early.
Absolutely.
I'm counting on you.
Come first.
We'll go to the options first.
Mom, it's morning.
It's 10:00.
Morning Lardis.
Morning La Ladissez.
It's only available this winter.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll have this today.
At 10:00 in the morning.
Kimcheese in the morning
Together, one cup at a time.
One cup each.
That's right.
We've been here a long time.
I see.
That's right.
Not at noon.
I eat at 10:00.
Oh, you don't want to eat.
I'll have to skip breakfast.
I'm gonna go to 7-Eleven and grate some curry.
Yeah, grated curry... in advance.
And then after I eat my ramen.
I'm going to do sit-ups.
I'll do sit-ups.
Thank you very much for watching.
Congratulations!
Now, I'm going to do sit-ups on the fourth floor, and then I'm going to come to the information desk.
Information?
You can sit in the information area now.
What?
It's not a rest area.
Oh, no.
Information about life.
I'm not here to give you information.
I'm here to welcome you to your new home.
When you say life information, you mean...
What life information?What's Life Information
You say that like it's the title of a single.
Oh, that's interesting.
To welcome the information
I'm here for the real information.
I was thinking we should break up.
You're breaking up?
Wait a minute.
Come to the Oppeshan at 10:00.
You'll be on the fourth floor doing sit-ups.
There are stairs.
We'll go downstairs, we'll go up, we'll go downstairs, we'll go up, we'll go up.
We'll sit down at the information desk, and then we'll break up.
This date ends at 10:20, right?
Well, I'm sure you're happy.
That's not what I meant.
It's just information.
It's just a synopsis.
I'm scared.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, that concludes my date plan.
Yay!
Please definitely skip to the end and come back with the two of us holding hands!
That's how my date plan ended!
You've seen the two of us...
I said confrontation, but...
But they both have their own merits.
I'm not saying which one was better.
I'm not saying which one was better, but if you're watching this
If you want to comment on which one was better, please do so.
I'd like you to actually do it.
I'm begging you.
I'd like you to do it, but
I can't sit in the JFCC.
I can't do it.
You'll have to substitute it elsewhere.
There are other things about the E-beads that I can't introduce.
I can't even begin to introduce them to you.
I got lost today, didn't I?
What do you mean?
That's right.
There are lots of clothing stores
There are lots of carronations.
We can pretend to be animals.
There are lots of cafes.
There really are a lot of good stores.
Please cooperate with us!
Please write your own comments and tell us what you would do.
I'd like to see what you would do if you were me.
I'd like to see it.
I'd love to hear your comments!
Please do!
Well, that's all for today's exploration.
Thank you very much.
It's over.
I remembered.
Bye-bye.
Please subscribe to our channel.